{
    "id": "b929d20825e746b1bee072248bba2062",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………… she could not meet the deadline, she lost her job.",
            "description": "All of these words show the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Since",
                "Because",
                "All of these"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "9f00e60c7dfd45628c3b5569f58aa143"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Why are you leaving?’ ‘I am leaving …………………………… I have had enough of this nonsense.’",
            "description": "When the reason is the most important part, use because.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "since",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "327130b1a09a454a8ca39c9ed360fb73"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… it was a holiday, I didn’t get up until 2 pm.",
            "description": "As shows the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "So",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "94ddc094a6164f4f861167dbdab6c777"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t seen him ………………………… Friday.",
            "description": "Since indicates the starting point. It is commonly used with the present perfect tense.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "833798b9b3ce4c0a94f998d022657ed9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He didn’t pass the test …………………………….. he hadn’t studied well.",
            "description": "Because shows the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "99f84184d3044c9193cefa7693acb2a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was limping ……………………….. she had injured her foot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "37fdfecb2b104d09921ee54585c0a9d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has broken his leg …………………………….. he can’t walk.",
            "description": "So shows the effect.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "because",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eb64c0a06e4d4814ad9fe0226f9cf7c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been several months …………………………….. it rained.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f079750bd1d643e4b3825f0bf594e731"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was unhappy ……………………………. she was lonely.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81e0dbc15a2e421ab13465991c2bbc17"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat ran away ……………………………. it was afraid.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "hence",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "77df903161ed437a9c702d60bdf6256a"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… she studied well, she passed the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "As",
                "Since",
                "All of these"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "52d8890f3c644d7f93e618192c8cd25f"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was raining …………………………. we stayed at home.",
            "description": "So shows the effect.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "as",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "adc4f92724044aa0b08384dbb5296617"
        }
    ]
}